



« I've always been fascinated by new technologies and how to use them in the best possible way. During the last years, I always programmed keeping up to date with the latest developments. I worked for some companies while staying organized and motivated. »

+33 7 83 40 27 03 Phone: E-Mail: moise.yoann@gmail.com Website: http://www.yoann-moise.com

## Work Experiences

#### **CRM Lead & Full Stack Developer**

Reezocar - Paris, France

SINCE OCT. 2016

I've built from scratch and managed the own made CRM of this fast-growing startup, which is used everyday by more than 60 employees.

Most of the sales and after-sales tasks have been automatized in order to focus more on the client's satisfaction

I was developing in React|S & GraphQL 75% of the time and managed projects 25% of the time.

#### **Software Engineer**

Sopra Steria - Sophia Antipolis, France

FROM SEPT. 2015 TO SEPT. 2016

I improved my skills in JavaEE and GWT on a project started from scratch and ordered by the French government to build the biggest retirement management system existing.

#### Semantic Web Internship

CNRS & INRIA - Sophia Antipolis, France

FROM MAY 2014 TO AUG. 2014

I contributed to the media part of a web app based on the research subject: Question Answering WikiFramework-based System.

It allowed me to work with semantic standards (RDF-S/OWL/SPARQL) with more common languages (Java, JS, REST, JSF).

#### Freelance

#### France

FROM JAN. 2012 TO MAY 2016

As a Freelancer, I've developed Web (JS, PHP, or Word-Press) and Android (JAVA) apps for clients in France, Italy, Tunisia and USA.

I built myself a network alongside my studies, which allowed me to learn how to deal with clients.

## **Education**

#### Master's Degree in Business Informatics

Université Nice Sophia Antipolis, France GRADUATED IN 2016

#### **Erasmus Exchange in Business Informatics**

Københavns Universitet. Denmark

GRADUATED IN 2015

#### **Summer School**

European Innovation Academy, Nice, France 2015

# { Skills }

#### Web Development

ReactJS, GraphQL, SQL, JavaScript, PHP, REST

#### **Project Management**

Team Management, Agile Methods

### Software Development

Java, Python, C

#### Semantic Web Development

RDF-S, SPARQL, OWL

### Languages

French (C2)

English (C1)

Italian (B2)

Romanian (A2)

Spanish (A1)

# Volunteer

I\*ESN (Erasmus Student Network) **Rotaract Club** Leo Club

Sicania

Travel Photography Genealogy Mixology Sports

Interests

#### **Publications**

"Nice, Regards Croisés", June 2011

Find more about me on my website

